<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Richard Murphy]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Michael Richard Murphy]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/michael-richard-murphy/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 02:52:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/michael-richard-murphy/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Try What If Instead of If Only]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Try What If Instead of If Only</h1><p>An entrepreneur recently posed a question to a group I’m a part of and asked, “What is insert his city missing?” The issue is that while he has had some successful ventures, success in his city is apparently not the norm. Not for startups anyway. To be honest, I’m not sure success is the norm for startups anywhere but there’s no denying certain areas of the country seem to have more than their fair share of it. While my city, Rochester, is not his city, I think there are some aspects which are very similar and this is a legitimate question if you live anywhere other than New York City, Boulder or Silicon Valley.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/michael-richard-murphy/try-what-if-instead-of-if-only/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">829723a1-67bc-4914-ae5d-f56a3687d036</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 02:51:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Good enough gets it done]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Good enough gets it done</h1><p>It was 2008 and I was living in the mountains of Oregon and working remotely for a company headquartered back in my home state of New York. I had about three friends in Oregon when I moved and because I was telecommuting, I didn’t have the baked in social network that work provides. So I spent a lot of my non-work time by myself exploring all the amazing things Oregon has to offer like tons of hiking and mountain biking. But it was after a particularly nasty mountain bike crash that I had a revelation. It would be really easy to die, or at least get seriously injured, in the mountains doing some of the stuff I liked to do and nobody would ever know where I was. And since I didn’t have a huge social circle at the time it could be days before anyone even thought to look for me.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/83aab59d65ef55cca59b12d1e005fad3e4f4dbf6.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/michael-richard-murphy/good-enough-gets-it-done/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c0de2567-b972-4bed-b28c-653d84cfba3b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 02:51:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Even The Ordinary Has Value]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Even The Ordinary Has Value</h1><p>My grandfather's straight razor</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/70065417f9249f2b1599d7a8bae15ff717881cb9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/michael-richard-murphy/even-the-ordinary-has-value/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9ac292e1-b506-4da9-a376-1bb8507a9db9</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 02:52:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Broken Windows]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Broken Windows</h1><p>I first heard about broken windows in Paul Graham’s book Hackers and Painters. Broken windows was originally a criminology theory along the lines that obvious neglect and disorder breeds more neglect and disorder. We’ve all seen abandoned buildings full of broken windows. They didn’t start out that way. Most people would be reluctant to throw the stone that breaks the first window. But once one or two are broken, and not replaced, that apparent apathy makes it easier to continue the trend. It slowly erodes that “barrier to entry”. People who wouldn’t ordinarily do something like that possibly consider it because, after all, it’s obvious that nobody cares. Before you know it, all the windows are broken. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6c9d0ee8b199ba78dfe5b2daf88f442a2213acab.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.michaelrichardmurphy.com/broken-windows/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">74e9ace4-f5aa-4f03-b72d-d0bc9dd00ac9</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 02:32:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fake It 'Til You Make It]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Fake It 'Til You Make It</h1><p>We’ve all heard that catchphrase and frankly, I think it gets a bad rap. Maybe it’s because when the word ‘fake’ is applied to things it usually means a cheap or low quality knockoff. And fake people are phony or superficial. So fake as a descriptor isn’t exactly a ringing endorsement.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/33b63a84eda0fb1d1d9789abec6db9cccf77b91b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.michaelrichardmurphy.com/fake-it-til-you-make-it/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">00bb800d-812c-4161-9a1e-d3641d15efab</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 02:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Good Spaces and Third Rooms]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Good Spaces and Third Rooms</h1><p>I was introduced to the idea of good spaces and third rooms a few weeks ago during a talk at TEDxBuffalo and I’ve been fascinated by the concept ever since. I think it stuck with me because it finally provided a name for a concept I had been thinking about but couldn’t really identify.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/michael-richard-murphy/good-spaces-and-third-rooms/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">17b724b4-40e2-4514-bef2-3891bcfe292e</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 02:29:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>